Полина Гагарина - Shallow
Tell me something, girl
Are you happy in this modern world?
Or do you need more?
Is there somethin' else you're searching for?
I'm falling
In all the good times I find myself
And in the bad times I fear myself
Tell me something, boy
Aren't you tired tryin' to fill that void?
Or do you need more?
Ain't it hard keeping it so hardcore?
I'm falling
In all the good times I find myself
Longing for a change
LongIng for a change
We're far from the shallow now
In the sha-ha, sha-hallow
In the sha-ha, sha-la-la-la-low
We're far from the shallow now
In the sha-ha, sha-hallow
I'm off the deep end, watch as I dive in
We're far from the shallow now
I'll never meet the ground
I'm off the deep end, watch as I dive in
Crash through the surface, where they can't hurt us
I'll never meet the ground
We're far from the shallow now
Crash through the surface, where they can't hurt us
In the sha-ha, shallow
We're far from the shallow now
In the sha-ha, sha-la-la-la-low
In the sha-ha, shallow
We're far from the shallow now